[ eerie music playing ]
ANCHOR : ... has hinted that it could be only the beginning .
WOMAN : Hi , honey , you 're home !
ANCHOR : In a seemingly related story , a Lebanese citizen ...
WOMAN : Starting to worry . I wondered where you were .
MAN : Get off my back . Hear me ?
WOMAN : I just wondered if you had a good day .
MAN : Please , get off my back !
WOMAN : Stop screaming !
MAN : Fuckin ' shut up !
WOMAN : Fine .
MAN : Charlotte !
ANCHOR : A Miami jury today returned a guilty verdict
In the slaying of abortion doctor Irwin Guffer .
It took the seven-man , five-woman jury
only a matter of hours to find ...
Mother !
[ rock music playing ]
[ urinating ]
[ screams ]
[ laughing ]
Hey ! God !
Hey , Charles , I think you 're chasing
the wrong tail there , buddy .
Oh , my God ! Where have you been ? We 've been waiting .
The Wedding 's going on inside .
We need to put you on the top tier .
Don 't mind the footprints in the icing .
I 'm excited . They look good .
It 's like a vest thing . I fucking hate kids .
Miss Abbott , did Barry come through here ?
Barry ? Oh , Barry .
- Didn 't you break up ? - No !
Oh , well , never mind . I just thought ... Forget it .
She 's doing it again .
Miss Abbott , she just does that to make trouble , okay ?
It is obvious . It is so
- What are you talking about ? - Obvious .
Don 't even listen to a word she says .
She 's just trying to make trouble .
All that ... All that ... All that ... All that ...
It 's just that she 's such a bitch !
- Sean , hi . - Hey .
Have you seen Barry ?
- Not in a while . Have you ? - No .
She was , like , completely naked .
Oh , bullshit .
No , she was spit on all over the place .
It was like a battleship or something , you know ?
Sol lay her down ...
- A battleship ? - Okay , like a dinghy .
Has anybody seen Barry ?
Have you seen Barry ?
- Barry ! - Oh , shit !
Heather ! Shit !
Don 't worry about it , Barry . She 'll be back .
If that 's really what you want .
[ starts engine , tires squeal ]
BARRY : Heather ! Heather ! Heather , stop !
Heather ! Stop the car !
Heather !
Damn it , Heather !
Heather , you better fuckin ' stop this car right fuckin ' now !
Damn it , if we have a wreck , it 's gonna be my ass !
- HEATHER : I don 't care . - BARRY : Slow down , please .
I wasn 't doing anything .
I don 't know what you 're so pissed off about .
Barry , I saw you . You were kissing her .
" BARRY " . Once . I kissed her once . What 's wrong with that ?
Come on , it 's like I can 't even talk to my friends anymore .
I can 't believe how possessive you are .
Oh , right . I guess that 's why you were feeling her up .
Look , guys need sex , okay ? It 's bad for you
to get all worked up and then not get it .
You can get " prostrate " cancer . Is that what you want ?
- That 's a lie . - [ screaming ]
- [ Girl ] Heather , look out ! - [ tires screeching ]
Heather !
- [ horn honking ] - [ screaming ]
[ crashing ]
- Fuck ! - [ tires squealing ]
BARRY : What the fuck is the matter with you ?
I 'm dead . I 'm so fuckin ' dead right now .
Oh , man .
You can 't get cancer from not having sex .
Oh , right . Like you 'd know .
You never had a date in your life , you 're so ugly .
- SEAN : She is not . - BARRY : Shut up , Sean .
He 's just trying to make you think it 's your fault .
Look , my father 's a doctor , okay ?
I think I know what I 'm talking about , so fuck you , Jenny .
It 's true . It is my fault . I won 't have sex with him .
That doesn 't make it your fault .
Yeah , but what if he gets cancer
and all his hair falls out from all the drugs or something ?
It could happen .
Yeah , Jenny , so just shut up , all right ?
" JENNY " . No , that 's just a line to get you to have sex with him .
- Ask Sean . - SEAN : She 's right .
He 's never had a hard-on in his life .
" SEAN " . I know all his lines .
He lived across the street from me till the eighth grade .
Shut up , Sean .
We were even friends before he got too cool ,
so fucking annoying .
BARRY : Hey , it 's not my fault
you turned out to be such a little geek .
He used to come over to my house all the time
and he 'd be laughing about all the girls he 'd felt up .
His big line was to tell ' em that his father was a doctor ...
and that they could get breast cancer
if they didn 't get felt up enough .
- Barry ! - Okay , I lied . Big deal .
It 's not my fault they 're stupid enough to believe it .
- JENNY : What a schmuck . - What 's your problem , Jenny ?
Just ' cause you hate guys .
He 's just tryin ' to change the subject .
What are you afraid of ? That they might try to fuck you ?
No .
It 's not like it 's a big secret .
- What ? - BARRY : Ask anybody .
You never go to parties . You never go anywhere
unless you 're with Sean .
Everybody knows that he 's a little pothead
and all you are is friends .
By the way , I know what you 're doin ' in my car .
You 're gettin ' stoned .
If my dad smells this shit tomorrow ,
I 'm gonna kick your ass .
Wait , wait , wait .
I just thought of something so cool .
What if we got into a wreck
and we crashed into a car in front of us and we all died ?
They could write a song about it .
Shut up .
[ eerie music playing ]
- BARRY : Where the hell are we ? - SEAN : Oh , great . We 're lost .
HEATHER : No , we 're not . All we have to do is go back .
JENNY : Look for a place where we could turn around .
Cool dress , Jenny . What 's this ?
Stop -
BARRY : What 's the matter ?
Afraid somebody might find out you have tits ?
Barry !
- Girls have tits . - SEAN : Leave her alone , Barry .
There 's no place to turn around .
There 's never any place to turn around . This sucks .
These assholes don 't know how to make roads .
What was that ? Did you all see that ?
- [ gasps , screams ] - Watch out !
[ crashing ]
Oh , no . I 'm so dead .
- Is he okay ? - I don 't know .
God !
- This is gonna leave a scar . - [ gasps ]
- I 'm not hurt . I 'm not hurt . - [ door closes ]
- Oh , shit . - His head .
Oh , my God ! Is he dead ?
Did he die ?
No , he 's just passed out . You can tell by his eyes .
Yeah , but he could be in shock . We need to get him to a doctor .
Yeah , right . And keep him warm .
- All right . - How did you know that ?
Something bad 's gonna happen . I can feel it .
He 's gonna die . Look at him .
Do you think it 'll start ?
[ starts engine , puts in reverse ]
[ tires spinning ]
[ turns off engine ]
[ engine grinding ]
I 'm dead . Somebody kill me , please .
HEATHER : It 's my fault .
If he dies , I 'll be a murderer .
[ engine continues grinding , stops ]
We 've gotta find someplace where we can call an ambulance .
- I 'll go . - Okay , come on .
I 'm not stayin ' here alone . What if he dies ?
Fine , then I 'll go with you .
You stay away from me .
This is stupid . Look , I 'm gonna go ,
and whoever wants to come , come .
- But somebody needs to stay . - I don 't know what to do .
Wait . Do you have a flashlight ?
[ eerie music playing ]
Is somebody gonna come with me ?
[ footsteps approaching ]
[ wings flapping ]
- Stop ! I heard something . - Heather .
I had these dreams about some weirdo
following me through the woods ,
- and it 's coming true . - Yeah ?
I 'm sorry , but we 're all gonna die .
Mm-hmm .
Some murderer , like that guy in Chicago .
He killed people and put their hearts in a refrigerator .
He 's gonna kill us .
They 're gonna show our pictures , naked ...
with our hearts torn out on A Current Affair .
[ sighing ]
God . What was that ?
[ flashlight clattering ]
BARRY : Great . Now we can 't see jack .
I 'm sorry , but someone is following me .
I can feel their eyes on my back .
- Bullshit . - No , that 's what they want .
For us to go wandering around in the dark .
We need to stay here and start a fire .
We need to call an ambulance .
We can 't do anything until we can see .
[ kids screaming ]
[ eerie music playing ]
Thank God . We 're saved . Somebody say a prayer .
Piece of shit .
You might be , but my father is still gonna kill me .
[ country music playing ]
Call the police . There 's been this horrible accident .
A man 's dying .
Prom night .
Somebody bring me a glass of water , please .
Quick . I 'm think I 'm gonna pass out .
Goddamn answering machine .
Don 't you worry . He 'll pick up .
Vilmer , if you 're there , babe , pick up the phone .
Vilmer .
Phony as three-dollar bills .
Changed my life , though .
Goddamn it , Vilmer , button it up , babe .
- Get me some water . - Stop it .
You know what ? The minute I showed up with these ...
every peanut farmer in the county
thought he was God 's gift to women .
What the hell .
- Doubled my commissions ... - Okay .
In the first six months .
Goddamn it . It 's about time . Vilmer , listen .
Some kids got in a wreck up the road ,
and one of ' em 's hurt .
Uh-huh . W-w-wait-wait a second , wait a second .
- Which way ? - Back that way .
- How far ? - About a mile .
About a mile back up 709 from me .
Uh-huh .
All right . Bye .
Why do blondes stick their heads out of car windows ?
- HEATHER : Why ? - Get a refill .
I don 't get it .
Airheads ?
[ laughing ]
" JENNY " . We should get back then and see if Sean 's okay .
BARRY : Yeah .
[ glass shatters , girls scream ]
- BARRY : What was that ? - Don 't worry about it .
Just some farmer 's wife .
Like I 'm even interested . See ' em and weep !
[ horn honking , boys cheering ]
Or some high school boy .
You know , they are always doin ' somethin '
to get me to flash ' em .
- BOY : Worse . - SEAN : What ?
- [ Vehicle Approaching ] - Hey !
Hey , is there an ambulance coming ? This guy 's hurt .
I think he 's delirious .
[ hydraulics whirring ]
Is he okay ?
Boy 's dead .
No , he 's not . He 's just passed out .
I said he 's dead .
But he was just talkin ' , like talkin ' in his sleep .
Is that right ?
Well ...
[ breaks neck , chuckles ]
[ eerie music playing ]
He 's dead now .
[ hydraulic leg whirring ]
Boy , don 't even think about running off down that road .
It ain 't gonna do you a damn bit of good ,
I can tell you that right now .
What are you gonna do ?
Well , first , I 'm gonna kill ya .
It ain 't no fuckin ' biggie .
' Course , it 's different for every individual .
[ starts , revs engine ]
[ indistinct conversation on radio ]
Sorry I can 't give you all a ride .
That wrecker 'll be along before you know it .
- Thanks for calling for us . - Yeah , thanks .
Oh , hey ! Don 't you worry about
that old boy that drives the wrecker .
He talks tough ,
but you just tell him how the cows eat the cabbage ...
and you won 't have any trouble .
Okay . Thanks a lot .
Hey , what about the service station across the road ?
You think maybe somebody there could give us a ride ?
WOMAN : That old man ?
Oh , he is liable to shoot first and ask questions later . Hey !
We see you , you old fart .
Thanks . Bye .
[ door closes ]
[ truck approaching ]
[ laughing ]
You tired yet , boy ?
Please , mister , you 're scaring me .
No shit .
[ panting ]
What did I do ?
Let 's just say you 're shit out of luck , son .
Just tell me what I can do . Give me a chance .
Oh , we ain 't even havin ' fun yet , son .
[ laughing ]
[ gear grinding , engine revving ]
Run , run , run !
Swing right .
[ gasping ]
Come back to Papa . Now .
- [ truck accelerating ] - [ yelling ]
All right , racing fans .
Here ... We ...
[ rock music playing ]
- [ revving engine ] - Go !
[ Laughing ] Oh !
Oh !
♪ This is what I want ♪
Oh , Still kickin ' !
[ groaning ]
VILMER : That should have done it .
Yes , that should have done it .
[ rock music fades ]
[ eerie music playing ]
HEATHER : Barry , there 's somebody out there .
I mean it this time . I 'm not making it up .
Stop . Listen .
BARRY : I don 't hear anything .
HEATHER : Jenny , stop ! My feet hurt .
BARRY : What am I supposed to do , carry you ?
HEATHER : Carry me piggyback . Just for awhile .
BARRY : Lose 20 pounds . Yeah .
Oh . Oh , man . All right . This guy 's a lifesaver .
Hey ! Hey , hey .
Come on , man . Wait . Hey , man , wanna give us a ride ?
All we need is a ride . We 'll pay you .
[ music playing in car ]
HEATHER : Jenny !
Barry , wait ! We could get arrested for trespassing .
[ owl hooting ]
[ eerie music playing ]
[ owls hooting ]
- No . - [ banging flashlight ]
Heather !
Barry !
- [ banging flashlight ] - Please , come on .
[ sighs ]
Hey , if you guys can hear me ,
I 'm gonna go back and see if Sean 's okay .
All right ?
- [ vehicle approaching ] - No , wait !
- Hey ! - [ motorcycle departing ]
[ eerie music playing ]
[ sighs ]
[ footsteps ]
Okay , who 's there ?
Is there anybody there ?
[ screaming ]
[ gasping ]
[ laughing , sighs ]
Barry , wait . Stop .
What if they 're murderers
and they want us to follow them ...
so they can hide behind trees and stab us ?
There could be dead people buried all around us ,
and we 'd never know .
They could tie us up in a cellar and no one would ever hear us .
That 's dumb .
There aren 't any cellars in the houses around here .
Okay , that 's it . Don 't call me dumb , Barry .
I may not be the smartest person in the world ,
but I 'm not stupid .
I just act that way sometimes
to get people to like me , that 's all .
Yeah , right .
All those stories about murderers
and people following me . I know it 's not true .
It 's better than being bored . I 'll tell you what 's stupid ...
is that line you gave me about you and that girl , Brenda .
Not even a little kid would believe that .
Jenny , that bitch . She started this whole thing .
It 's all her fault .
You 'd like to think . I 'll tell you what it is . I 'm a bitch .
I 'm just like my mother . She can 't stand my father .
But she stays with him because
she wants a certain kind of life .
I don 't care what anybody thinks .
That 's still the best way to get it .
What 's wrong with that ?
Forget it .
Okay , fine , but you should 've said something .
It pisses me off that you let me go on like this .
It 's embarrassing .
I told you , I 'm a bitch .
If I wasn 't such a chicken , I 'd be more like Jenny .
No , you wouldn 't .
- You 're probably right . - She 's a dog .
- Oh , huh ? You just don 't know . - What ?
Everyone thinks she 's such a wuss , right ?
Right .
Her mother gets married every 15 minutes ,
and her husbands are always hitting on her .
That 's why she 's the way she is , but I 've had P.E. with her .
- She 's got a body to die for . - Really ?
[ eerie music playing ]
[ owl hooting ]
Sean ?
[ hooting continues ]
JENNY : Sean ?
- Great . - [ rattling flashlight ]
[ sighs ]
HEATHER : Tell them we 'll give ' em 50 bucks
if they give us a ride , okay ?
BARRY : Fifty bucks ?
HEATHER : You don 't have to give it to them .
Tell them to send us a bill .
If they get mad , give ' em five bucks .
Tell ' em we 'll send the rest later .
It 's no big deal .
Just business . My father does it all the time .
BARRY : You are weird .
- [ knocking ] - Hey , is anybody home ?
Hello ?
Must be deaf .
- [ knocking ] - Hey , is anybody in there ?
Maybe they 're out back .
Well , go check .
Hey , I have an idea ! Why don 't I go check ?
Bitch .
[ kicks door ] Ow ! Damn it !
[ sighs ]
[ radio playing softly ]
[ insects chirping ]
[ eerie music playing ]
MAN : Hold it right there .
It 's okay . We had a wreck . All we want is a ride .
[ cocks rifle ]
You better not shoot me , mister .
There was a man that shot a kid who was robbing his house ,
and they got him for murder .
" I propose to fight it out on this line "
" if it takes all summer . "
That 's Ulysses S. Grant .
You probably didn 't know that , did you ? ' Course you didn 't .
' Cause you 're a bona fide moron .
Come pokin ' your nose around here where it don 't belong .
[ eerie music continues ]
[ groans ]
[ broom clattering ]
- [ screaming ] - [ screaming ]
[ both screaming ]
Heather !
It 's okay . She 's my girlfriend .
- [ Heather struggling ] - Don 't trouble yourself .
[ screaming ] Barry !
[ continues screaming ]
[ both screaming ]
[ gasping ]
[ yelling , pounding ]
[ screaming ]
[ gasping ]
- [ crying , screaming ] - [ yelling ]
[ gasping ] , screams ]
[ yelling ]
[ screaming ] No ! No !
[ continues screaming ]
No ! Stop !
[ gasping , screaming ]
[ crying hysterically ]
- [ grunting ] - No !
No !
[ Screaming ] No !
Please ! No .
No !
Please ! Please !
[ screaming ]
[ muffled screaming ]
No ! Please !
[ continues screaming ]
[ panting , yelling ]
[ continues yelling ]
- [ Heather screaming ] - [ Panting ]
- [ screaming continues ] - [ screaming ]
[ dog barking in distance ]
Hey , if I go in there , that 's kidnapping .
My father 's a lawyer .
I know what I 'm talkin ' about , okay ?
" Among other evils that being unarmed brings you ... "
" it causes you to be despised . "
That 's Niccolo Machiavelli . Now get !
Okay , okay . I need to use your bathroom , anyway .
Dumb-ass !
Heather , you in here ?
Heather ?
[ eerie music playing ]
I need to piss . Where the hell 's the bathroom ?
[ light clicks on ]
Heather ?
Heather , you okay ?
- [ sighs ] - [ lifts toilet seat with foot ]
There 's some crazy guy outside with a shotgun .
Locked him out , though . You should 've seen me .
[ unzips fly , sighs ]
[ urinating ]
[ sighs , zips fly ]
[ sighs ]
[ gasping ]
Fuck !
- Heather ? - [ yelling ]
What 's goin ' on in there ?
[ continues screaming , yelling ]
[ screaming ]
[ moaning ]
[ grunting ]
[ continues grunting ]
[ Heather , muffled ] Barry ? Who 's out there ?
- Please ! No ! - [ screaming ]
- [ Leatherface screaming ] - [ Heather screaming ]
- [ Screaming ] - No ! No ! No ! No !
[ both continue screaming ]
- [ Squishing ] - [ gasping ]
- [ Whimpering , crying ] - [ yelling ]
- [ groaning ] - [ yelling continues ]
[ sinister music playing ]
VILMER : You don 't need to be walkin '
these roads alone this time of night .
Why don 't you get in ?
Are you the one that moved the cars ?
Listen , either you want a ride or you don 't . It 's up to you .
Where are you goin ' ? Where 's Sean ?
- Where do you wanna go ? - Where 's Sean ?
- Is that your boyfriend ? - Yeah .
He was the one that wasn 't hurt . Do you know where he is ?
I know exactly where he is . Now why don 't you get in ?
Well , where is he ?
Goddamn it ! I said get in the truck .
Well , wait a second . Hang on .
[ engine rumbling ]
[ Vilmer clears throat ]
Yeah .
You gotta watch
gettin ' into cars with strangers these days .
I heard about an old man once ,
picked up a little girl on the side of the road ...
chopped both her arms off , stuffed her in a culvert ,
left her for dead .
- God , I fuckin ' hate that . - Yeah .
I mean , that sorry son of a bitch
didn 't have shit for an imagination .
How fuckin ' simple can you get ?
- Stop . You 're scarin ' me . - Scarin ' you ' ?
You 're not scared .
You don 't know shit about bein ' scared , little girl .
Not yet .
You want scared ? You want scared ?
Have a look behind you . Have a look .
Yeah , how about that , huh ?
- Look again , goddamn it ! - No !
Go ahead , look again !
No ! I think I want you to stop and let me out .
[ laughing ] You think ? Or do you know ? Huh ?
Go ahead and have a look .
- Gotcha a better look . - No .
- You don 't wanna look ? - No . No .
What 's your goddamn problem ?
- [ laughing ] - Okay . If you stop , I 'll look .
[ tires skidding to stop ]
- You wanted to stop . - Stop it ! Ow ! Ow !
Come on , have a look at that .
Have a look at that . Take a look at that .
How ' bout that ? What is that ?
What is that ? Huh ? Huh ?
[ Vilmer laughing ]
- [ gasps ] Oh , God ! - [ continues laughing ]
Yeah , of course , you gotta throw in a little somethin ' extra ...
just to let ' em know it ain 't Saturday mornin ' cartoons ,
if you know what I mean .
[ laughing , puts truck in gear , accelerates ]
What 's gonna happen to me ?
You think I give a goddamn what happens to you ?
Are you letting me go ?
You figure it out . It 's your goddamn life .
I don 't understand .
Well , welcome to the real world .
[ eerie music playing ]
[ laughing ]
[ groans ]
[ gasping ]
[ rock music playing ]
[ chuckling ]
- [ panting ] - [ truck accelerating ]
[ laughing ]
[ gasps ]
[ whimpering ]
You don 't know what the hell you 're doin ' .
Just where do you think you 're goin ' ?
[ turns off truck ]
VILMER : Okay .
If that 's what you want ...
it 's up to you .
Live and learn .
- [ starts truck , laughing ] - [ rock music playing ]
[ truck departing ]
[ insects chirping ]
[ sniffling and whimpering ]
- [ rustling ] - [ gasping ]
[ panting ]
[ panting continues ]
- [ chainsaw revving ] - [ Leatherface screaming ]
[ screaming ]
[ both screaming ]
- [ crying hysterically ] - [ chainsaw buzzing ]
[ screaming , crying ]
Oh ! Oh , shit , no ! Oh , God , no !
- [ crying ] - [ yelling ]
[ chainsaw buzzing ]
[ Crying hysterically ] No ! No ! God , no !
[ continues crying ]
[ crying hysterically ]
- [ chainsaw revving ] - [ Leatherface yelling ]
Somebody !
- [ continues sobbing ] - [ revving continues ]
- [ screaming , revs chainsaw ] - [ sobbing ]
[ chainsaw continues ]
- [ Leatherface screaming ] - [ revving chainsaw ]
- [ gasping ] - [ screaming ]
- [ pistol clicks ] - [ screams , revs chainsaw ]
- [ chainsaw continues ] - [ pistol clatters ]
[ screaming ]
[ gasping ]
[ grunting ]
[ screaming ]
[ crying ]
[ screaming , revving chainsaw ]
[ grunting , screaming ]
- [ screaming ] - [ screaming , revving chainsaw ]
[ crying ]
- [ Leatherface screaming ] - [ revving chainsaw ]
[ screaming ]
[ insects chirping ]
[ dog barking in distance ]
[ owl hooting ]
[ chainsaw buzzing ]
[ glass shattering ]
- [ gasping ] - [ screams , revs chainsaw ]
- [ panting ] - [ chainsaw buzzing ]
[ rock music playing ]
[ chainsaw revving ]
[ Panting ] Oh , God .
- [ clattering ] - [ screaming , crying ]
[ sobbing hysterically ] Open this door !
- What in the world ? - Oh , God .
- It 's okay . It 's okay . - He 's out there .
No , no , it 's fine . It 's all right .
Just ... just come here . Come here .
Just sit down . Sit down , right now .
I 'm gonna go see what 's what . No . It 's gonna be all right .
Now just sit there . I 'll be fine . Now , listen .
I 'm just gonna go put a little scare into ' em .
All right , you got any balls , show your face .
[ panting , sobbing ]
It 's been a long night , boys .
I could use a little action .
[ country music playing ]
[ footsteps approaching ]
It 's nothin ' .
No , he 's out there with a chainsaw .
No , he had a chainsaw . He was chasing me with a chainsaw .
Listen here . It 's just local boys
tryin ' to give you a little scare , that 's all .
No , the guy with the wrecker killed Sean .
Hell 's bells . It 's party time . What about your friends ?
I don 't know . They tried to get a ride .
W.E. , what the hell is goin ' on ?
Where 's Vilmer ? Hey , I don 't wanna hear it .
You get your butt over here mucho-quicko . All right .
I tell ya , that old man , his nerves are shot . Now listen .
Don 't you worry .
Vilmer does something , it 's for a good reason .
- Who 's Vilmer ? - Good question .
Hey , you know what ? You look real pretty
- with your glasses off . - [ footsteps approaching ]
- What ? - Well , what ...
You should 've brought a gunnysack or somethin ' .
What 's this look like to you ? Green eggs ?
Well , what the hell you waitin ' for ? Tie her up !
Hey ! You sit right down here , little lady .
I got enough trouble .
[ cattle prod zapping ] [ screams ]
Goddamn it , W.E. Now look what you got started .
Wait till Vilmer hears about this .
I swear to God .
- [ cattle prod zaps ] - [ screams ]
- [ laughing ] Go ! - [ cattle prod Zapping ]
Where 's my gun ?
[ blow lands on Jenny ] [ groans ]
- [ blows landing on Jenny ] - [ screaming ]
It is easier to resist at the beginning than at the end .
[ crying ]
Be sure to tell Vilmer I 'm gonna stop off at the pizza place
and pick us up some dinner , all right ?
- [ cattle prod zapping ] - [ crying ]
JENNY : Why are you doing this ?
" Conversation is a game of circles . "
- [ cattle prod zapping ] - That 's Ralph Waldo Emerson .
- [ continues zapping ] - [ continues crying ]
What if I was to turn you loose , huh ?
What would you give me , huh ?
What do you think about that , huh ?
JENNY : What do you want ?
- What do you want ? - I 'll tell you what I want .
W. E. , what the hell are you doin ' back there ?
[ mutters , claps hands ]
- I tell you what . - [ sobbing ]
Grow up , will you ?
[ sobbing continues ]
And tell Vilmer I called our order in
so it would be ready when I got there ...
and then I 'm comin ' straight home .
- [ cattle prod zapping ] - [ screaming ]
[ engine rumbling ]
Okay , we got one medium deluxe ...
one medium pepperoni , one large vegetarian .
And your drinks 'll be out in a minute .
- Okay . - [ Jenny ( muffled ) ] Help me !
- Uh , lady ? - Uh-huh .
I think you got something in your trunk .
That 's just somebody I got tied up back there .
- Really ? - Uh-huh .
Really , what 's back there ?
You wanna come see ?
Sure .
I ... I better not . I might get in trouble or something .
All right .
Will you shut up and quit kickin ' my car .
JENNY : Okay , but I can 't breathe .
TEEN : Welcome to Bud 's . Can I get your order , please ?
Uh , what do you want ? Coffee ? Black coffee ?
OFFICER : Yeah .
- Uh , two black coffees . - TEEN : Is that all ?
If I poke a hole for you , you gonna quit ?
JENNY : Uh-huh .
- Well , somebody 's gotta do it . - In your dreams .
Now if I hear any more kickin ' or screamin ' ...
I 'm gonna come back here
and tape your mouth shut , all right ?
- JENNY : Okay . - Okay .
[ trunk shuts ]
What you got in the car , honey ?
[ chuckles ]
Believe me , you don 't wanna know .
Oh , come on now , I 'm a nice guy .
Uh-uh-uh ...
Ma 'am . Your drinks are ready .
[ shifting gears , tires squealing ]
[ pop music playing ]
[ gasping ]
[ car engine stops ]
[ Heather coughing ]
What are you doin ' out here in the middle of the road ?
[ gasping ] Please , help me .
All right .
But I gotta run and go get a blanket or something first .
You stay right there .
[ gasping ]
Please , don 't hit me . Don 't !
[ crying ]
Don 't hit me .
Stop !
Okay -
But don 't you go crawlin ' off .
[ continues crying ]
[ car door shuts ]
[ crickets chirping ]
[ music playing in distance ]
[ horn honking ]
[ horn honks ]
[ sobbing quietly ]
[ screaming ]
Get ! I said , get on out there . Move !
- Leave him alone . - [ cattle prod zapping ]
You run along and do whatever W. E. Tells you .
He even tries to hit you , you let me know ...
and I 'll tell Vilmer .
" I have not yet begun to fight . " That 's John Paul Jones .
You might can scare him , but you so much as lay a finger on me ...
you 'll wish you 'd never been born .
[ whimpering ]
Oh , hey , almost forgot . One of ' em got away .
She 's crawlin ' off down the road .
You better get her , too .
[ whimpering ]
Come on . Bring her in .
I 'm not gonna hurt you .
I 'm not gonna hurt you . See ? I 'm not gonna hurt you .
See ? I 'm right here . Not gonna hurt you .
Go on . Get in there . Move !
- [ cattle prod zapping ] - [ screaming ]
Get ! Get !
[ cattle prod continues zapping ]
- [ screaming ] - Hi , sweetie . How was your day ?
Sweetie , would you shut up ?
What are you so pissed off about ?
Huh ? You having a bad day , huh ?
Why are my batteries not charged ?
Did W.E. tell you ?
That son of a bitch . I tell you what .
I told him to let you know
that I was on my way for pizzas on the way home ,
and he didn 't tell you , and I 'm sick of it .
[ grunting , gasping ]
Look what your brother did to this door .
Nobody gives a damn about that door .
Hey , mister , I have had it with you .
I 'm so sick and tired of you tryin '
to stir up trouble between me and Vilmer .
You 're the one causin ' problems .
Ever since you got here , you been nothin ' but trouble .
DARLA : Nobody gives a goddamn about the door .
I 'm the one who puts things together here .
- DARLA : Nobody cares . - It was fine before you come .
I said shut up .
[ whimpering ]
My God .
What are you gonna do ?
You don 't fuckin ' believe this , do you ?
Oh , God . What are you gonna do to me ?
You know , I asked you a goddamn question .
He asked you a goddamn ...
You don 't think the FBI has this place
under 24-hour surveillance ?
You don 't think there 's transmitters in all these walls ?
[ Jenny mumbling incoherently ]
Let me ask you one question .
- Are you havin ' fun yet ? - Oh , God !
[ laughing ] Because I promise you ...
I promise you , you and I are gonna have some fun .
- Oh , no . No more , please . - [ laughing ]
- No . Ow . - What 's my fuckin ' name ?
[ whimpering ]
- What is this ? What is this ? - I don 't know . I don 't know .
I don 't know !
- [ crying ] - You don 't know ?
- You don 't know shit , do you ? - No . No .
- [ crying ] - [ laughing ]
Do you think all I want to do is kill you ?
I don 't know .
You 're goddamn right you don 't .
[ crying gagging ]
- [ Jenny crying ] - [ Vilmer panting ]
Hey , why don 't you just try to relax a bit , honey .
I know it 's hard .
Why don 't you mind your fuckin ' business ?
Look at this fucking door .
[ sobbing ]
[ continues sobbing ]
What ?
" The woman 's a whore ,
" and there 's an end on it . "
That 's Samuel Johnson .
Oh , take it on out of here .
Now , now .
Don 't you let him get to you , ' cause that 's what he wants .
[ crying ]
Will you please tell me what all this is for ?
Well , you 'll have to ask Vilmer that .
But if you ask me ,
I think the son of a bitch is from outer space .
[ Heather whimpering ]
[ muffled screaming , whimpering ]
Oh , God . What are you gonna do ?
No , what are you gonna do ?
[ groans ]
- Don 't hurt her . - Give her a kiss .
How could I hurt a pretty face like this , huh ?
But then , I am in the mood for love .
[ screaming ]
- [ both girls screaming ] - [ cattle prod zapping ]
[ screaming , zapping continue ]
[ laughing ]
There , now .
How 's that ? Feel better ?
[ music in background ]
[ sighs ] Look at you .
You 're really pretty .
You know what ? I have got this dress
that I have never even worn and it would be perfect on you .
[ crying ]
Oh , you 're scared .
- I just don 't want to die . - Well , of course you don 't .
Will you help me ?
VILMER : Shut up in there .
Hey , you just hush up yourself . It 's just girl talk .
I tell you what . He 's not near as bad as he seems ,
once you get to know him .
It 's just this job . You know , all the stress .
It 's his job to kill people ?
Well , I really shouldn 't be telling you this .
But you know how you always hear these stories
about these people who run everything ,
but nobody knows who they are , right ?
Well , it 's true .
I mean , I never would have believed it , but it 's all true .
I mean , who do you think killed Kennedy ?
Government ?
No , that government stuff is bullcrap .
It 's these people .
And they 've been doing this kind of thing for , like , a thousand ,
or two thousand years , I forget which .
And nobody , I mean nobody , knows their names .
And that 's who Vilmer works for .
[ door opening ]
I told you ... goddamn it !
[ ominous music playing ]
[ sniffs ]
Alone again , huh ?
[ groans ]
- Little desert flower . - [ grunting ]
I 've got a mind ...
to slit your goddamn throat .
Give you a count to ten to give me a reason why I shouldn 't .
- Nine , eight , don 't be late . - What ? Oh !
[ groaning ]
Seven , six , you better get it right .
- I don 't want you to kill me . - [ sniffing ]
- Five , four . - [ gasping ]
Three , two .
Yes , you want me alive for some reason !
Huh ?
You want me alive for some reason .
- [ gasping ] - That 's a good answer .
[ kisses ] That 's a good answer .
Smart girl . We 've got us a smart girl .
Well ...
it kind of makes you think , doesn 't it , smart girl ?
[ unlatches door ]
[ Darla , Vilmer fighting ]
[ gasping , shuddering ]
Wrong , wrong .
[ yells ] ' [ grunts ]
You 're embarrassing me in front of company !
No , no , no , no , no !
[ indistinct shouting ]
Don 't you ever touch me !
[ Darla continues shouting ]
[ crying ]
[ shouting ] , crying continue ]
Okay , stop !
- [ commotion continues ] - Nobody move , or I 'll shoot !
- [ Leatherface whimpering ] - VILMER : What did she say ?
" Nobody move , or I 'll shoot ? "
W.E. : You want my advice ? Gut-shoot him .
Poison his insides . Otherwise , it won 't do no good .
He 's been shot before . Lots of times .
Run over . It don 't mean spit .
Oh , shut up , W.E. Nobody asked you .
You shut up !
All the time , runnin ' your big mouth .
No , everybody shut up !
Why don 't you shut up ?
JENNY : Okay , now get down on the floor .
Everybody get on the floor
and put your hands in front of you !
- Get down ! - Okay .
[ Leatherface whimpering ]
You get down , too .
What are you gonna do , shoot me ?
Yeah , if you try something .
[ opens knife ] What if I do this ?
Goddamn it , Vilmer ! That ain 't one bit funny !
- Stop it ! - [ slapping ]
Now , we 're gain ' . Now , we 're gain ' .
What do you think , huh ?
One , two . Take your fuckin ' chances .
- It 's a damn trick . - Shut up , W.E.
W.E. : Why don 't you shut up your own self ?
Oh , God . Just forget it , hon .
I tell you , if that shotgun was anywhere
where you could get at it , believe me , it 's what he wanted .
No . You stop .
You get back down .
" Discretion is the better part of valor . "
That 'd be Billy Shakespeare .
You get down too , or I 'll kill you .
- Come on . - Hey , I 'm sorry , sweetie .
I got a big mouth . What can I say ?
Okay , maybe it 's not loaded .
But maybe it is , so fuck you .
And if you come near me , or if you try to stop me ,
I 'm gonna blow your fuckin ' head off !
Hey , let 's not make this an all-nighter , all right ?
I mean , I hate to be a party pooper ,
but it 's late and I 'm tired and the pizzas are getting cold .
And nobody asked you fuckin ' shit !
[ slams Darla to floor ]
- [ Leatherface howling ] - [ Vilmer grunting ]
[ gasping ]
Heather . Heather , get up . Get up , Heather .
You have to get up . We 're gonna go .
Five more minutes .
- Get up , Heather ! - [ Darla gasping ]
JENNY : You 're gonna kill her !
[ screaming ]
[ W.E. talking indistinctly ]
- [ laughing ] - Heather , come on . Get up .
[ maniacal laughing continues ]
I can 't find my shoes !
Heather , come on . It 's okay . Get up .
No , Heather . No , you got to get up .
You got to get up now . We have to get out of here .
Stop it !
[ groaning ]
- [ shotgun clicks ] - [ laughing ]
Pop goes the weasel .
[ shotgun blasting ]
[ shouting ]
[ yelling ]
[ crying ] Oh , my God !
[ starts car ]
[ bluesy music playing ]
VILMER : What are you doin ' in there , little girl ?
[ laughing ]
[ hysterical crying , mumbling ]
VILMER : Hey , what are you doin ' there ?
Whoa !
JENNY : Oh , God !
[ Jenny whimpering ]
[ car crashing ]
[ groaning , panting ]
[ ominous music playing ]
[ screams ]
Damn shame about her face , Leather .
Least you can have her shoes .
[ hydraulic whirring ]
Look who 's comin ' to visit .
Come on up and have a good time .
We want to see that that doesn 't happen again .
No ! [ Crying ]
- Don 't get excited . - [ whimpering ]
[ thudding from blow ]
[ W.E. laughing ]
That ought to settle her down for a while .
- [ crickets chirping ] - [ ominous music playing ]
[ singing in German ]
[ oven bell dings ]
You better be nice to me .
' Cause I can always go back to my husband .
[ hydraulic whirring ]
[ clattering ]
Is that all you got ? Huh ? Huh ?
[ grunts ]
[ panting ]
[ hydraulic whirring ]
Better come eat before it gets cold .
All right , all right , all right .
- What took you so long ? - [ sniffs ]
Welcome to my world .
I suppose we can forget about having a nice , quiet evening .
[ slapping ]
- [ blues music playing ] - [ sniffing ]
[ screaming ]
[ both screaming ]
[ all screaming ]
[ grunts ]
- [ whimpering ] - [ mimics whimpering ]
[ continues mimicking ]
Just go ahead and breathe into this .
Go ahead .
- [ crying ] - Breathe . Breathe .
Yeah . Yeah .
- [ breathing into bag ] - Yeah .
I told him once , I told him a thousand times ,
it 's gonna end in tears .
You lie down with dogs , you 're gonna get up with fleas .
Any fool ought to know that .
" Common sense is not so common . " That 'd be Voltaire .
All right .
Are you gonna help me or not ?
[ mimics Jenny ] Are you gonna help me or not ?
And don 't tell me any more of your stupid stories .
Hon , you just don 't understand .
[ laughs ] He doesn 't work for anybody .
- Shh . Shh . - [ whimpering ]
The only reason for any of this
is that he 's a psycho and he gets off on it .
[ whimpering ]
Get off . Now listen . I just can 't .
See , he put this little thing in my head ...
and all he has to do is push one little button , and , and , and ...
[ mimics explosion ] blow my head clean off .
- [ mimics explosion ] - [ mimics explosion ]
[ laughing ]
There 's nothing in your head .
Girl , you just said a mouthful .
[ giggling ]
You get to runnin ' with the wrong crowd ,
wind up in the reformatory .
No respect . No discipline . That 's the problem .
Family values have gone straight to hell .
- Now , for why we came . - [ yells ]
My brother here is tired of what 's-her-name 's face ...
and he wants a new one .
It just happens to be he wants this face right here .
- [ gasping ] Oh , no ! On , no ! No ! - Oh , yeah ! Oh , yeah !
' No ! Oh ' Yes !
Yes , it does .
Don 't you touch me !
Don 't you ever touch me !
[ panting ]
[ sniffling ]
If you 're gonna kill me , then do it !
I 'm not gonna put up with any more of your crap .
It 's bullshit . Nobody believes any of it ...
except your idiot girlfriend !
It 's fucking pathetic !
[ yells ]
[ Darla whimpering ]
There is nothing to fear but fear itself .
[ yells ]
Now , I 'm gonna leave ...
and no one is gonna stop me .
[ screams ]
You sit the fuck down !
- [ whines ] - JENNY : And shut up .
VILMER : Are we havin ' a party or what ?
Here we go !
Douse her down !
Oh , please ! No , you can 't do that ! No !
- She had nothing to do with it ! - That doesn 't matter .
- I 'm sorry ! - Fire in the hole !
- Burn ! - No !
Watch her burn ! Watch her burn !
[ Heather screaming ]
Burn !
[ continues screaming ] VILMER : Burn !
[ throws matches ]
[ crying ]
Now , Why 'd you have to do that ?
You know I can never get that smell out of my clothes .
- [ horn honks ] - Oh , God . Oh , God
[ Jenny crying ]
JENNY : Oh , God , no .
Well ...
what the hell do you want ?
I assume that that is a rhetorical question .
You assume whatever you goddamn well please .
It ain 't no skin off my ass .
Is that what you want me to think ?
That you 're a silly boy ?
[ sighs ]
Oh , God . Oh , God . Oh , God , you have to help me .
These people are crazy . Please , come on . Let 's go .
- Let 's get out of here . Please . - It 's all right . Shush . Shush .
There , there . There , there . Come on , now . Come on .
Come on . Shh . There .
That 's better . Shh .
Come on , now . Shh . Shh . Come on .
It 's all right . It 's all right .
Just sit down . There you go .
- There . That 's all right . - [ sighs ]
There , that 's fine . You just stay there .
It 's gonna be fine , okay ?
Come on , now . Shh , shh . It 's all right .
- [ hyperventilating ] - It 's all right . Come on .
There , see ?
[ grunts ]
What is this ?
No ?
Can anybody else tell ?
[ Vilmer 's hydraulics whirring ]
Things are gonna change .
- [ grunts ] - I can promise you that .
You just sit there .
- No . No . No , don 't go , please . - You just sit there .
[ sobbing ] No .
[ crying ]
[ grunting ]
Fuck !
This is appalling .
[ grunting ]
You are here for one reason ...
- and one reason only . - [ grunts ]
Do you understand that ?
I want to hear you say you understand that .
- [ grunting ] - No ?
It 's very simple .
I want these people
to know the meaning of horror .
Horror .
- Is that clear ? - [ grunts ]
You don 't want to be a silly boy .
Is ... that ... clear ?
[ whimpering ]
Fuckin ' A it is .
JENNY : What ...
What ... What are you ...
What are you doing ?
Why a woman like you has anything to do ...
with this ...
cripple ...
is a mystery to me .
Bastard , you know exactly why I 'm here .
[ grunting ] , sniffs ]
[ Jenny gasping , crying ]
What are you , what are you gonna do ?
Oh , God . I don 't want anything ! Oh , no !
[ whimpering ] Oh , god . Oh , no !
[ sobbing ]
[ crying ]
[ kicks trash ]
[ groaning ]
- [ sobbing ] - [ Heather whimpering ]
- [ skull cracking ] - [ Heather screaming ]
[ cracking , screaming continue ]
- [ hydraulics whirring ] - [ Heather whimpering ]
- [ whirring continues ] - [ skull crushes ]
[ sobbing ]
What ? What ?
DARLA : What are you doin ' now ?
Don 't . It 's not your fault ! Stop that !
- [ rock music playing ] - Stop it .
- Stop . It 's not your fault ! - [ Leatherface screaming ]
Don 't !
Don 't ! Please don 't !
[ Leatherface screaming ]
[ chainsaw revving ]
[ window shatters ]
[ screaming ]
[ chainsaw revving ]
[ Jenny screaming ]
[ hydraulics whirring ]
[ hydraulic remotes dueling ]
- [ chainsaw revving ] - [ Leatherface screaming ]
[ continues whirring ]
- [ screaming ] - [ groaning ]
[ all screaming ]
[ rock music playing ]
VILMER : Get her , Leather ! Get her , Leather !
- We got some more fun today ! - [ chainsaw revving ]
[ screaming ]
[ remote clatters to floor ]
[ hydraulics whirring ]
Vilmer !
Get that bitch !
Go !
- [ rock music playing ] - [ airplane engine revving ]
- Thank you , Mrs. Spottish . - [ clinks glasses ]
MRS. SPOTTISH : It 's a beautiful morning .
[ chainsaw revving ]
[ gasping ]
- Stop ! Stop ! - Don 't stop ! Don 't stop !
Stop ! Please stop ! Oh , God , no !
[ chainsaw revving ]
There 's a monster chasing her with a chainsaw !
[ Jenny screaming ]
MRS. SPOTTISH : Step on it , Mr. Spottish !
- [ screaming ] - [ Jenny panting ]
[ screaming ]
- [ indistinct screaming ] - Step on it !
[ crashing ]
[ insects chittering , birds chirping ]
[ airplane engine rumbling ]
[ rock music playing ]
[ gasping ]
[ Leatherface screaming ]
[ thudding ]
[ groans ]
[ Leatherface screaming ]
[ chainsaw revving ]
[ gasping ]
[ screaming , revving chainsaw ]
[ horn honking ]
[ screaming continues ]
- [ panting ] - [ door closes ]
[ Leatherface whimpering ]
Oh , no , no , no , no . You have nothing to fear .
[ speaking French ]
[ whimpering ]
[ chainsaw idling ]
- [ revving chainsaw ] - [ whimpering ]
[ screaming ]
MAN : This ...
all of this ... [ sighs ]
It 's been an abomination .
You really must accept my sincere apologies .
It was supposed to be a spiritual experience .
I can 't tell you how ...
disappointed I am .
I suppose it 's something we all live with .
People like us who strive for something ...
a sense of harmony .
Perhaps it 's disappointment that keeps us going .
[ speaking French ]
Unfortunately ...
it 's never been easy for me .
One of my many failings .
Fuck you .
Would you like to go to the local hospital ...
or to a police station ?
You know , this isn 't the first time
something like this has happened .
Miss ? Miss ?
We will find out what this is all about .
This is not the end of it .
Miss ? Miss ?
Do you know who that is , miss ?
Miss ?
What the hell is going on around here ?
[ rock music playing ]
- [ screaming ] - [ chainsaw revving ]
[ roots music playing ]